<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>looker studio on James Buckley</title>
    <link>/tags/looker-studio/</link>
    <description>Recent content in looker studio on James Buckley</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© James Buckley</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/looker-studio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Analysing WhatsApp Data with BigQuery and Looker Studio</title>
      <link>/post/whatsapp-metrics/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/whatsapp-metrics/</guid>
      <description>WhatsApp is one of the most popular messaging apps in the world, with over 2 billion active users. It’s no surprise that many people want to analyse their WhatsApp data to gain insights into their conversations, including myself! In this post, I’ll detail how I used Python and BigQuery to analyze my WhatsApp data, covering everything from parsing the raw TXT export to visualizing the data. Let’s get started!
Parsing the TXT Export Within WhatsApp it is possible to export chat data to a TXT file, by opening the options within individual or group chats, tapping &amp;ldquo;More&amp;rdquo; then &amp;ldquo;Export chat&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lighthouse Gauges for Data Studio</title>
      <link>/post/lh-gauge-datastudio/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/lh-gauge-datastudio/</guid>
      <description>Site speed metrics can be obtained using the Lighthouse auditing tool, which can be run within Google Chrome. Metrics like this have started to become used in SEO ranking, so naturally if efforts are being made to improve site speed, it makes sense to measure and report on it. When tasked with creating a dashboard displaying Lighthouse metrics over time, what better way to display the current score for each metric than in the very same gauges Lighthouse itself uses in its reports:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
